Finding Aid for the Tony Barrett Papers PASC.0061
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 2. Radio scripts and production material
  - Screen Directors' Playhouse (NBC, 1949-1951)
    - D.O.A. by Jack Rubin, 1951 June 21 (Box 105, Folder 15)
    - STAIRWAY TO HEAVEN by Richard Alan Simmons, 1951 July 21 (Box 105, Folder 16)
    - MRS. MIKE, 1950 November 21 (Box 105, Folder 17)
  - Screen Guild Players (ABC, 1950-1951)
    - NO TIME FOR COMEDY by Harry Kronman, 1951 April 5 (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - TOGETHER AGAIN by Harry Kronman, 1951 May 3 (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - The Silent Men (NBC, 1951-1952)
    - THE ROPING OF JOE LANDIS by Lewis and Rusoff, 1951 November 21 (Box 116, Folder 7)
    - VISAS FOR SALE by Lewis and Rusoff, 1951 December 10 (Box 116, Folder 8)
  - The Six-Shooter (NBC, 1953-1954)
    - RINK by Frank Burt, undated (Box 116, Folder 9)
    - ANNA NORDQUIST by Frank Burt, 1954 March 12 (Box 116, Folder 10)
  - Song of Liberty
    - GENERAL WASHINGTON, undated (Box 116, Folder 1)
    - Script, 1951 May 22 (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - Stars over Hollywood (NBC, 1950-1951)
    - I KNEW THIS WOMAN by Helen Morgan, 1951 September 26 (Box 106, Folder 17)
      Starring Joan Crawford.
    - UNDER CONTROL by Roderick Peterson, undated (Box 106, Folder 24)
    - THE EXPERIMENT by John McGrevey, 1952 May 20 (Box 116, Folder 4)
      Starring Angela Lansbury.
    - I WANT TO GO TO NANTUCKET, 1951 February 3 (Box 116, Folders 5)
    - ADVICE FROM ANN, 1953 April 2 (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - Suspense (CBS, 1940-1962)
    - RED CLOUD MESA, 1956 (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - THE FLAME, 1956 (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - EYE WITNESS by William N. Robson, 1956 December 12 (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - BACK SEAT DRIVER, 1955 (Box 103, Folder 4)
      Also includes a slightly different version of the script dated 1951 February 22.
    - THE GREATEST THIEF IN THE WORLD, 1951 June 21 (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - I'M WALKING ALONG HUMMING, undated (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - THE FLAME-BLUE GLOVES by E. Jack Neuman from the story by Lois Eby and John C. Fleming, 1949 (Box 103, Folder 7)
    - DUTCH SCHULTZ by James Poe, 1953 October 26 (Box 103, Folder 8)
    - THE STEEL RIVER PRISON BREAK, 1951 (Box 103, Folder 9)
    - A MISFORTUNE IN PEARLS, 1951 (Box 103, Folder 10)
    - MESSAGE TO GARCIA by Richard Chandlee, 1953 August 30 (Box 103, Folder 11)
    - MADMAN OF MANHATTAN by Gilbert Thomas, undated (Box 103, Folder 12)
    - THE MAN WHO THREW ACID, 1956 (Box 103, Folder 13)
    - MURDER IN G-FLAT, 1951 March 19 (Box 103, Folder 14)
    - QUIET NIGHT, 1956 (Box 103, Folder 15)
    - OVER THE BOUNDING MAIN, 1950 (Box 103, Folder 16)
    - OVER THE BOUNDING MAIN, 1955 (Box 103, Folder 17)
    - REMEMBER ME, 1955 (Box 103, Folder 18)
    - SAINT JAMES INFIRMARY BLUES, 1953 (Box 103, Folder 20)
    - THE SHOOTING OF BILLY THE KID, 1952 (Box 103, Folder 20)
    - STRANGE FOR A KILLING, 1955 (Box 103, Folder 21)
    - EARLY TO DEATH, 1951 April 12 (Box 103, Folder 22)
    - SEE NO EVIL by Anthony Barrett, undated (Box 103, Folder 23)
    - WINDY CITY SIX, 1951 January 20 (Box 103, Folder 24)
    - THE STOOL PIGEON, 1955 (Box 103, Folder 25)
    - DONOVAN'S BRAIN, 1944 May 18 (Box 110, Folder 8)
  - Tales of the Texas Rangers (NBC, 1950-1952)
    - THE DEVIL'S SHARE by Joel Murcott, undated (Box 107a, Folder 1)
    - THE TRAP by Joel Murcott, 1951 February 20 (Box 107a, Folder 3)
    - DEATH PLANT by Charles E. Israel, 1951 December 4 (Box 107a, Folder 4)
    - ALIBI by Arthur Browne, Jr., 1952 June 28 (Box 107a, Folder 5)
    - FINGER MAN by Charles E. Israel, 1952 June 11 (Box 107a, Folder 6)
    - NIGHT HAWK by Charles E. Israel, 1952 March 15 (Box 107a, Folder 7)
    - SMART KILL by Anthony Barrett, 1952 April 3 (Box 107a, Folder 8)
    - BLOOD TRAIL by Charles E. Israel, 1951 December 24 (Box 107a, Folder 9)
    - CLIP JOB by Charles E. Israel, 1952 January 3 (Box 107a, Folder 10)
    - THE ICEMAN by Charles E. Israel, 1952 February 5 (Box 107a, Folder 11)
    - TRAVESTY by Betty Mears, 1952 April 5 (Box 107a, Folder 13)
    - ILLUSION by Charles E. Israel, 1952 February 23 (Box 107a, Folder 14)
    - CON MAN by Betty Mears, 1952 March 8 (Box 107a, Folder 15)
    - COVER-UP by Bernard Ederer and Robert A. White, 1952 May 17 (Box 107a, Folder 16)
    - TRIAL BY TERROR by Bernard Ederer and Robert A. White, 1952 July 10 (Box 107a, Folder 17)
    - DOUBLE EDGE by Charles E. Israel, 1952 June 26 (Box 107a, Folder 18)
    - STICK UP by Bernard Ederer and Robert A. White, 1952 June 21 (Box 107a, Folder 18a)
    - THE BLOW-OFF by Tom Blackburn, 1951 November 10 (Box 107a, Folder 19)
    - SQUARE DANCE by Joel Murcott, 1951 May 8 (Box 107a, Folder 20)
    - NIGHT CHASE by Charles E. Israel, 1952 January 12 (Box 107a, Folder 21)
    - ROUND TRIP by Charles E. Israel, 1952 May 24 (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - THREE VICTIMS by Charles E. Israel, 1952 July 3 (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - DEATH SHAFT by Bob Ryf, 1951 September 24 (Box 108, Folder 3)
    - JOY RIDE by Joel Murcott, 1951 May 14 (Box 108, Folder 4)
    - JAIL BIRD by Charles E. Israel, 1952 April 24 (Box 108, Folder 5)
    - LITTLE SISTER by Charles E. Israel, 1952 February 14 (Box 108, Folder 6)
    - UNCERTAIN DEATH by Charles E. Israel, 1952 March 6 (Box 108, Folder 7)
    - DRIVE-IN by Charles E. Israel, 1952 July 17 (Box 108, Folder 8)
    - COLD BLOOD by Charles E. Israel, 1952 January 22 (Box 108, Folder 9)
    - HELPING HAND by Joel Murcott, 1951 October 18 (Box 108, Folder 10)
    - NO LIVING WITNESSES by Joel Murcott, 1951 April 24 (Box 108, Folder 11)
    - SELL OUT by Betty Mears, 1952 May 8 (Box 108, Folder 12)
    - PRELUDE TO FELONY by Betty Mears, 1952 February 26 (Box 108, Folder 13)
    - MISPLACED PERSON, undated (Box 108, Folder 14)
    - HITCH-HIKER by Lawrence Goldman, 1952 January 17 (Box 108, Folder 15)
    - KILLER'S CROP by Bob Ryf, 1951 December 8 (Box 108, Folder 16)
    - DREAM FARM by Shelby Gordon, 1952 February 16 (Box 108, Folder 17)
    - THE RUB OUT by Will Gould, 1952 January 19 (Box 108, Folder 18)
    - PICKUP by Charles E. Israel, 1951 December 13 (Box 108, Folder 19)
    - EX-CON by Charles E. Israel, 1952 May 15 (Box 108, Folder 20)
    - KNOCKOUT by Charles E. Israel, 1952 May 22 (Box 108, Folder 21)
    - ILLEGAL ENTRY by Charles E. Israel, 1952 May 3 (Box 108, Folder 22)
    - CHRISTMAS PAYOFF by Anthony Barrett, 1951 December (Box 108, Folder 23)
    - Notes, undated (Box 108, Folder 25)
    - TROOP TRAIN by Bernard Ederer and Robert A. White, 1952 March 13 (Box 108, Folder 26)
  - That Hammer Guy (Mutual, 1952-1954)
    - SCRIPT NO. 54 by Ed Adamson, 1954 (Box 111, Folder 5)
    - Script pages, 1954 (Box 114, Folder 1)
  - This Is Your FBI (ABC, 1945-1953)
    - THE INNOCENT SANTA CLAUSE, 1951 December 16 (Box 104, Folder 11)
    - THE HARVEST, 1951 September 21 (Box 104, Folder 12)
    - THE PROTECTION PEDDLERS, 1952 January 4 (Box 104, Folder 13)
    - THE CROSS-COUNTRY FUGITIVE, 1952 March 7 (Box 104, Folder 14)
    - SUCCESS STORY, 1951 March 16 (Box 104, Folder 15)
    - THE PROFESSIONAL KILLER, 1947 May 16 (Box 104, Folder 16)
    - OLD MOTHER LARCENY, 1951 May 18 (Box 104, Folder 17)
    - THE SWAMP KILLER by Robert Yale Libott, 1952 November 9 (Box 104, Folder 18)
    - CAPTAIN LARCENY, 1951 March 6 (Box 104, Folder 19)
    - HOT ICE, 1952 May 16 (Box 104, Folder 20)
    - THE TELL-TALE CAMERA, 1952 June 18 (Box 104, Folder 21)
    - KILLER FOR HIRE, 1952 May 14 (Box 104, Folder 22)
  - Time for Love (CBS, 1953-1954)
    - MARRAKECH MIRAGE, undated (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - True Detective Mysteries (Mutual/CBS, 1929-1958)
    - SINISTER FATE OF THE DOCTOR'S FOUR WIVES, March 1953 (Box 102a, Folder 15)
  - Tums Hollywood Theatre (NBC, 1951-1952)
    - A QUESTION OF TIME by Maurice Zimm, 1951 December 11 (Box 102, Folder 1)
      With Claudette Colbert.
    - THE LIVING END by Leonard St. Clair, 1952 (Box 102, Folder 2)
      With William Holden.
    - THE FIVE BUCK TIP by Harold Swanton, 1951 October 30 (Box 102, Folder 3)
      With Barry Sulivan.
    - THE THINGS THAT MONEY CAN BUY by Jack Laird, 1951 December 11 (Box 102, Folder 4)
      With Gary Merrill.
    - THE MAN ON THE THIRD FLOOR by Les Crutchielf [sic, probably Crutchfield], 1952 February 12 (Box 102, Folder 5)
      With Joseph Cotten.
    - SIXTY FOOT GRAVE by Anthony Barrett, 1951 November 13 (Box 102, Folder 6)
      With Tyrone Power.
  - The Whisperer (NBC, 1951)
    - THE WHISPERER, undated (Box 105, Folder 11)
  - The Whistler (CBS, 1942-1955)
    - Script, 1953 January 25 (Box 105, Folder 12)
    - THE CLIFFS OF WEYRUM by Adrian Gendot, 1955 June 23 (Box 105, Folder 13)
    - Script, 1953 April 5 (Box 105, Folder 14)
  - Wild Bill Hickock (Mutual, 1951-1956)
    - A SHOT IN THE DARK by Larry Hays, 1952 (Box 102a, Folder 1)
    - MISSION IN ALAMOGORDO by Larry Roman and Gomer Cool, 1951 August 22 (Box 102a, Folder 2)
    - CHALLENGE OF SENTINEL RIDGE, undated (Box 102a, Folder 3)
    - REVENGE OF THE RED MAN by Larry Hays, 1951 October 27 (Box 102a, Folder 4)
    - BAD MEDICINE by Paul A. Pierce, 1953 September 25 (Box 102a, Folder 5)
    - A TRAIL OF VENGEANCE by Larry Hays, undated (Box 102a, Folder 6)
    - TRAIL OF THE GRIZZLY BEAR by Paul A. Pierce, 1952 December 18 (Box 102a, Folder 7)
    - WINDMILL ON THE RIVER by Paul A. Pierce, 1952 December 16 (Box 102a, Folder 8)
    - THE HIGH-TONED STRANGER by Larry Hays, 1953 July 23 (Box 102a, Folder 9)
    - MADMEN OF MOON MOUNTAIN by Larry Hays, 1952 August 17 (Box 102a, Folder 10)
    - SCRIPT #7 by Doug Heyes, undated (Box 102a, Folder 11)
  - Your Nutrilite Radio Theatre (NBC)
    - BERLIN INTERLUDE, 1955 August 22 (Box 114, Folder 2)
  - Your Radio Theatre
    - THE LOST WEEKEND by Earl Hamner from the story by Charles Jackson, undated (Box 114, Folder 4)
  - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar (CBS, 1949-1962)
    - THE LONG SHOT MATTER EPISODE ONE by Tony Barrett, 1956 June 10 (Box 114, Folder 7)
    - THE LONG SHOT MATTER EPISODE TWO by Tony Barrett, 1956 June 10 (Box 114, Folder 12)
    - THE LONG SHOT MATTER EPISODE THREE by Tony Barrett, 1956 June 10 (Box 114, Folder 13)
    - THE LONG SHOT MATTER EPISODE FOUR by Tony Barrett, 1956 June 10 (Box 114, Folder 14)
    - THE LONG SHOT MATTER EPISODE FIVE by Tony Barrett, 1956 June 10 (Box 114, Folder 15)
    - THE MEDIUM WELL DONE MATTER EPISODE THREE by Jack Johnstone, 1956 April 29 (Box 114, Folder 16)
    - THE MEDIUM WELL DONE MATTER EPISODE FOUR by Jack Johnstone, 1956 April 29 (Box 114, Folder 17)
    - THE MEDIUM WELL DONE MATTER EPISODE FIVE by Jack Johnstone, 1956 April 29 (Box 114, Folder 18)
    - THE MONOPOLY MATTER by Gil Doud, 1951 February 3 (Box 114, Folder 19)
    - THE PEARLING MATTER EPISODE TWO by John Dawson, 1956 June 3 (Box 114, Folder 20)
    - THE PEARLING MATTER EPISODE ONE by John Dawson, 1956 June 3 (Box 114, Folder 21)
    - THE PEARLING MATTER EPISODE FIVE by John Dawson, 1956 June 3 (Box 114, Folder 22)
    - THE PEARLING MATTER EPISODE FOUR by John Dawson, 1956 June 3 (Box 114, Folder 23)
    - THE PEARLING MATTER EPISODE THREE by John Dawson, 1956 June 3 (Box 114, Folder 24)
    - THE JONATHAN BELLOWS MATTER by Blake Edwards, 1953 June 23 (Box 115, Folder 1)
    - THE LILILIS BOND MATTER by Gil Doud, 1951 May 17 (Box 115, Folder 2)
    - THE MALCOLM WISH, M.D. MATTER by Gil Doud, 1951 May 31 (Box 115, Folder 3)
    - THE TOM HICKMAN MATTER by Gil Doud, 1952 June 11 (Box 115, Folder 4)
    - THE TEARS OF NIGHT MATTER by John Dawson, 1956 May 6 (Box 115, Folder 5)
    - THE REASONABLE DOUBT MATTER by Les Crutchfield, 1956 May 28 (Box 115, Folder 6)
    - THE PRIMROSE MATTER by Les Crutchfield, 1956 September 23 (Box 115, Folder 8)
    - THE CRYSTAL LAKE CABIN MATTER by Robert Ryf, 1956 July 29 (Box 115, Folder 8)
    - THE BLACKMAIL MATTER by Blake Edwards, 1953 March 16 (Box 115, Folder 9)
    - THE CURSE OF KAMASHEK MATTER, 1956 August 5 (Box 115, Folder 10)
    - THE INDESTRUCTIBLE IKE MATTER by Jack Johnstone, 1956 May 20 (Box 115, Folder 11)
    - THE KRANESBURG MATTER by Les Crutchfield, 1956 July 30 (Box 115, Folder 12)
    - THE LAUGHING MATTER by Les Crutchfield, 1956 May 27 (Box 115, Folder 13)
    - THE ALDER MATTER by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 115, Folder 14)
    - THE ALDER MATTER by Tony Barrett, 1956 July 22 (Box 115, Folders 15-16)
- Series 3. Unproduced script material, clippings, and correspondence
  - Notes, undated (Box 78a, Folder 1)
  - LOG OF THE PANDORA by Tony Barrett and Paul Pierce, undated (Box 78a, Folder 2)
  - TWELVE GOOD MEN...AND SUE by Tony Barrett and Ross Murray, undated (Box 78a, Folder 3)
  - MEMORY GAME by John Neufeld and Lawrence Dobkin from a story by John Neufeld, Lawrence Dobkin, and Joanna Barnes, undated (Box 78a, Folder 4)
  - DON'T BE A SUCKER by Arthur E. Orloff, 1949 March 1 (Box 78a, Folder 5)
  - LIES OF SILENCE by Charles Kaufman and Franklin Coen, 1964 March 26 (Box 78a, Folder 6)
  - QUADRANGLE by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 78a, Folder 7)
  - SO FEW FOR LOVE by Ken Englund, undated (Box 78a, Folder 8)
  - HIMALAYA by Tony Barrett, 1964-1966 (Box 79, Folders 3-5)
  - HIMALAYA script pages, undated (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - THE MAN WHO CARRIED THE BALL treatment by Jack Jacobs and Tony Barrett, undated (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - HOME IS THE SAILOR treatment by Tony Barrett and Ross Murray, undated (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Notes and ideas, undated (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - THE FAT MAN outline, undated (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Story outlines by Peter Breck, R.N. Bullard, and Richard Nelson, undated (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Notes and outlines by Tony Barrett, circa 1962 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Ideas for Manhunt (Syndicated, 1959-1961), undated (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - NIGHTMARE outline by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - MAN WHO NEVER WAS [empty folder], undated (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Ideas for The Millionaire (CBS, 1955-1960), undated (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - THE LIE notes, undated (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - THE WALL outline by Anthony Barrett, undated (Box 82, Folder 13)
  - THE SHORT CUT outline by Ross Murray and Tony Barrett, undated (Box 82, Folder 17)
  - WANTED: DEAD OR ALIVE outline and correspondence, circa 1953 (Box 82, Folder 18)
    Apart from the title, this bears little resemblance to the Steve McQueen series that premiered in 1958, which Barrett also wrote for.
  - Collaborations with Het Manheim, 1959-1966 (Box 82, Folder 20)
    Includes story ideas and correspondence.
  - Whispering Smith (NBC, 1961) format description, 1958 September 22 (Box 82, Folder 21)
  - Comedy series treatment, 1960 (Box 82, Folder 22)
  - WIRE SERVICE outline, undated (Box 82, Folder 23)
  - KLONDIKE outline, 1960 May 24 (Box 82, Folder 24)
  - JUST MARRIED bible and character analysis, 1959 April 21 (Box 82, Folder 25)
  - Ideas for I Dream of Jeanie (NBC, 1965-1970), 1965-1966 (Box 82, Folder 26)
    Includes voluminous correspondence from Het Manheim, with little discussion of the show.
  - ENOUGH ROPE outline by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 82, Folder 27)
  - Idea for a crime series by Don Ingalls, undated (Box 82, Folder 28)
  - THE BROTHERS THREE outlines, 1972 (Box 83, Folder 3a)
  - CAL SAVAGE scripts, undated (Box 83, Folders 4-5)
  - EUROPEAN EYE, 1967 November 21 (Box 86, Folder 8)
    European Eye was intended to be a series for CBS. Though it was not picked up, the pilot was aired as a movie. It is not clear if this unattributed script is for the pilot or for an anticipated subsequent episode.
  - Clippings, 1972 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Contracts, 1956-1961 (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Contracts, 1954-1965 (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1963 (Box 87, Folder 7)
    Includes residuals statements.
  - Contracts, 1958-1959 (Box 87, Folder 9)
  - ROUGH BUCK outline and notes by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - Notes, undated (Box 87, Folder 10)
  - Notes and script pages, undated (Box 87, Folder 11)
  - Story ideas, circa 1955-1969 (Box 87, Folder 12)
    Includes two letters from Het Manheim to John Hawkins about Bonanza.
  - Notes, circa 1974 (Box 87, Folder 13)
  - Story ideas, undated (Box 87, Folder 14)
  - The Frankie Laine Show outline by Frankie Laine, E.J. Rosenberg, and Tony Barrett, undated (Box 87, Folder 15)
  - Notes, undated (Box 87, Folders 16-23)
  - The Joe Namath Show, 1971 March 10 (Box 88, Folder 1)
    Deposition detailing Barrett's involvement in this project.
  - EASY DAY by Robert Forrest and Tony Barrett, undated (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - THE PRESIDENT'S MAN outline and notes by Tony Barrett and E.J. Rosenberg, 1963 (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Number One World Way outlines and notes by Tony Barrett, 1961 (Box 88, Folder 4)
    Includes photographs and an LA Times supplement on LAX.
  - THE PIGEON outline, undated (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - THE KID outline for Trackdown (CBS, 1957-1959), undated (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - MIGHTIER THAN THE SWORD outline by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - THE GIMMICK outline and notes for Richard Diamond, Private Detective (CBS, 1957-1960), undated (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - A MATTER OF PRINCIPLE outline by Tony Barrett and Ross Murray, undated (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Hong Kong (ABC, 1960-1961) story ideas by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 88, Folder 11)
  - COMEBACK outline and notes by Tony Barrett, 1955 (Box 88, Folder 12)
  - Story ideas, undated (Box 88, Folder 13)
  - DANGEROUS ASSIGNMENT - LONDON outline by Tony Barrrett, undated (Box 88, Folder 15)
  - THE WAY OUT outline by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 88, Folder 16)
  - THE MT. SINAI STORY by Tony Barrett, 1959 April 11 (Box 88, Folder 17)
  - THE HIDDEN TRUTH outline by Paul Pierce and Tony Barrett for Judge Roy Bean (Syndicated, 1955-1956), undated (Box 88, Folder 18)
  - Story idea, undated (Box 88, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, 1954-1963 (Box 88, Folder 21)
  - Ideas for westerns, undated (Box 88, Folder 22)
  - Outlines and notes by Tony Barrett, circa 1962 (Box 88, Folder 23)
  - "Over-the-Hill Writer Plots Crime and Does It" idea, 1974 March 29 (Box 88, Folder 24)
  - Clippings and notes, 1962-1963 (Box 88, Folder 25)
  - Contracts, 1946-1959 (Box 88, Folder 26)
  - Clippings and notes, 1964-1969 (Box 88, Folder 27)
  - Scenes good but unused, undated (Box 88, Folder 28)
  - Teasers or shock scenes, undated (Box 88, Folder 29)
  - Methods of violence and death, undated (Box 88, Folder 30)
  - Notes, circa 1973 (Box 88, Folder 32)
    Includes performer popularity index.
  - Name change document, 1940 September (Box 88, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence, 1957-1965 (Box 88, Folder 34)
    Includes high school student responses to Barrett's play The Guitar.
  - THE HIGHEST WALL by Anthony Barrett, undated (Box 91, Folders 3-4)
  - Undercover Man outlines, 1959 (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - Nemo outlines and notes, 1962 (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - The Brothers Three outlines by Tony Barrett, 1972 (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Hunted Women script, undated (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - Thorns and Thistles playscript by Boris and Beatrice Greenberg, undated (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - G.P. script by Tony Barrett, 1955 March 3 (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - G.P. script and outline by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 93, Folder 10)
  - PORT OF CALL by Donn Mullally, 1955 December 27 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - The First Man treatment by Antony Ellis and Robert Forrest, undated (Box 94, Folder 16)
  - Mr. Moto notes and pilot script by Tony Barrett, 1964 (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - Mr. Domino scripts, outlines, and notes by Tony Barrett, Charles Beaumont, and Jim Barnett, 1963-1964 (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - THE ALLEN SAXTON MATTER by Tony Barrett from a story by Blake Edwards for Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar, undated (Box 96, Folder 10)
    Includes notes. This script appears to be an unrealized television adaptation of the popular radio show.
  - ECHO OF DEATH by Tony Barrett, circa 1961 (Box 96, Folder 11)
  - The Rhonda Fleming Show scripts, notes, and telegram, 1961 (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - THE POWERS TOUCH by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - Dangerous Assignment [empty folder], undated (Box 100, Folder 7)
  - One False Step by Tony Barrett, 1955 (Box 100, Folder 10)
  - Waterdogs by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 100, Folder 12)
  - The Walter Slezak Show by Tony Barrett, 1959 (Box 100, Folder 14)
  - Radio synopsis, undated (Box 107, Folder 22)
  - THE LINE-UP, 1950 July 13 (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - Crusader story line, undated (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - NO HIGHWAY IN THE SKY, undated (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - The Enchanted Room, 1951 February 21 (Box 111, Folder 13)
  - BRANDED, undated (Box 111, Folder 17)
  - The Adventures of Annie Oakley and Tagg (radio), 1951 October 6 (Box 111, Folder 19)
  - NIGHTMARE outline, undated (Box 112, Folder 1)
  - Story outline, undated (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - THE TIGER by Anthony Barrett, undated (Box 112, Folder 3)
    This script is for a proposed radio series starring Mabel Stark, the famed tiger trainer.
  - Untitled radio script, undated (Box 112, Folder 4)
  - Radio productions list, undated (Box 112, Folder 5)
  - Untitled radio scripts, undated (Box 112, Folders 6-7)
  - ARE YOU SURE? by Tony Barrett, 1943 (Box 112, Folder 8)
  - MANHATTAN MOUTHPIECE, undated (Box 112, Folder 9)
  - Script pages, undated (Box 112, Folder 12)
  - Radio script, undated (Box 112, Folder 13)
  - The Basic Principles of Good Writing Style, undated (Box 112, Folder 14)
    This document is an outline for an adult education course taught by Frances A. Rocklin.
  - Radio script pages, undated (Box 112, Folders 17-18)
  - THE GREAT SCOT (radio) by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 116, Folder 15)
  - PORTRAIT IN FEAR (radio) by Michael and Tony Barrett, 1948 (Box 116, Folder 16)
  - THEY ALSO SERVE outline, undated (Box 116, Folder 17)
  - Untitled radio scripts, undated (Box 116, Folders 18-19)
  - THE SMART KILL outline by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 116, Folder 20)
  - Untitled radio scripts, undated (Box 116, Folders 21-23)
  - Story outlines and treatments, 1965-1966 (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - Story ideas and story outlines, 1941-circa 1964 (Box 118, Folder 2)
    Includes government publications on Boulder Dam [Hoover Dam], the Grand Coulee Dam, and the Colorado River Aqueduct.
  - Story outlines, undated (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - Plotting notes and scene sequences, circa 1956 (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - Script pages revised, 1955-1958 (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - THE CASE OF THE ALTERED GUNS, undated (Box 118, Folder 6)
  - COCHIN TRADER, undated (Box 119, Folder 3)
  - Outlines by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 119, Folder 8)
  - DESPERATE GAMBLE by Tony Barrett (Box 119, Folder 9)
  - Streets of Laredo outlines by Archie L. Tegland, Calvin Clements, and John D.F. Black, 1965 (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Cheyenne outline by Tony Barrett and Paul Piece, undated (Box 120, Folder 5)
  - Pony Express outline by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 120, Folder 8)
  - The Captain by Tony Barrett, 1963 (Box 121, Folder 1)
    Includes Barrett's notes and script notes from Aaron Spelling.
  - Welcome to Paradise notes and outlines, undated (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - Two for the Money notes, undated (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - The Weird World of Wes Beattie notes and outlines by Tony Barrett, 1965 (Box 121, Folder 6)
  - T.H.E. Cat notes and outlines, undated (Box 121, Folder 8)
  - The Barefoot Boys outline by Walter Grauman, William Kayden, and Tony Barrett, undated (Box 121, Folder 9)
  - Canal Zone notes and outlines by Tony Barrett and Bud Kay, undated (Box 121, Folder 10)
  - Wait for Dark script by Dick Carr, undated (Box 121, Folder 11)
    Wait for Dark was to be a Danny Thomas/Aaron Spelling production created by Aaron Spelling and Dick Carr.
  - The Weird World of Wes Beattie notes, 1965 (Box 121, Folder 12)
  - Stories from periodicals, 1968-1969 (Box 121, Folder 13)
  - Mabel Stark outline (radio), undated (Box 121, Folder 14)
    Includes three photographs of tigers.
  - Dunham's Inc. notes, script, and correspondence, 1959-1961 (Box 122, Folder 1)